# **SHADAB SAIFI**

# **Architect-Environmental Planner**

Architect-Planner with specialization in Environmental planning from School of Planning and Architecture New Delhi, India. Worked on Projects like Energy efficient building

design and planning, Air and water quality modelling, management projects. Proficient in software like ArcGIS, Photoshop, AutoCAD.

## **Education**

**BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURE (2012-2017)** 

Government College of Architecture APJ Abdul Kalam Technical University Lucknow, U.P., India

**MASTERS IN ENVIRONMENTAL PLANNING (2017-2019)** 

School of Planning and Architecture New Delhi, India

## **Experience**

### **DELHI DEVELOPLMENT AUTHORITY NEW DELHI**

JUNE 2018–JULY 2018 ENVIRONMENTAL PLANNER • INTERN •

#### ARINEM CONSULTANCY NEW DELHI

JUNE 2015-DECEMBER 2015 ARCHITECT • INTERN

[Worked on Project like Yamuna Rejuvenation Delhi, Golden jubilee park Delhi, Group Housing, and Commercial Project, 3D-modelling.]

## **Research Interests**

Indoor & Outdoor Air quality modelling, Urban Heat Island, GHG emissions, Solid Waste Management, Energy Efficient Building Design, Energy Efficiency in Environmental Planning, Water Quality Assessment

## **Projects**

Water Resource Management Lucknow city
Environment Management Plan Bhopal City Region
Environmental Improvement Plan of East Kolkata Wetlands with focus
on Eco-system Services
Outline Development Plan- Kakinada Andhra Pradesh
Architectural Thesis on Cultural Center with Sustainable Approach



# **Contact**

- Hastinapur [Meerut 250404]
- +919457656735
- arshadabsaifi@gmail.com
- (ii) linkedin.com/in/shadabsaifi-265891b2

#### **Skills**

ArcGIS 85%

Photoshop 85%

MS Office 90%

AutoCAD

90%

SketchUp

90%

• • • • • • • • •